{
    "id": "1d87f733c51f47e38b6ff486e594cae8",
    "title": "Singular And Plural Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He weighs nine ……………………….",
            "description": "When the word score is used after a numeral, it does not have the plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "stone",
                "stones",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d261bc55edd94370b908157923869a72"
        },
        {
            "question": "That car cost me five ……………………… dollars.",
            "description": "When numerals like hundred and thousand are used after another numeral, they do not have the plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "thousand",
                "thousands"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d5091cba2d147a6aae4219220d30a61"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bought three ……………………… oranges.",
            "description": "When dozen is used after a numeral, it does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "dozen",
                "dozens"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c0bedb4f82044853b829e2712b0910e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "India won by …………………………. and three runs.",
            "description": "The noun innings is always used in the singular.",
            "answers": [
                "innings",
                "an inning",
                "an innings"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17a7c5033d744bf8be700b4e957e6d7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ………………………… small but he has no debt.",
            "description": "When means has the meaning of wealth, it is used in the plural.",
            "answers": [
                "mean is",
                "means is",
                "means are"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "43d30269238747239cb0bb64dfd21769"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. not only destroy our property but also carry disease.",
            "description": "The collective noun vermin is singular in form but it is always used as a plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Vermin",
                "Vermins"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d8eff18b1bab4e3ca492bd71858573b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………….. needs repairs.",
            "description": "The possessive case is chiefly used with the names of living things.",
            "answers": [
                "house roof",
                "house's roof",
                "roof of the house"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "19bf21f1d1264030b1066dc0375e09cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has no ……………………….. for his parents.",
            "description": "Respect means regard respects means compliments.",
            "answers": [
                "respect",
                "respects"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d86f79f6037840bf9bcf8428833f3dc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Both countries have withdrawn their ………………………..",
            "description": "Force means strength forces means troops.",
            "answers": [
                "force",
                "forces"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "03cb6d6c1a2d43059141fd54cc6ba2e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you always putting on ……………………….?",
            "description": "Airs can mean affected manners.",
            "answers": [
                "air",
                "airs"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26bcc7a859294edfbbe6772d0abd3a45"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must all stand up for the common ……………………",
            "description": "The common good means the interests of all.",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "goods"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0c0e707f66b14841a0bc0334d4cbcae7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wouldn’t listen to my ………………………",
            "description": "Advice means counsel advices can mean information.",
            "answers": [
                "advice",
                "advices",
                "advise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8d9719f4335949259e741a80d2289d28"
        }
    ]
}